<resources>
    <string name="app_name">L-CLAN</string>
    <string name="textfp1">\t\t\t\t\t<b> INFORMATION ABOUT JAVA </b>
        \n
        \t\t\t\t\t Java is a programming language and computing platform used for developing and running applications.
\n
        It was first released by Sun Microsystems in 1995 and has since become one of the most popular programming languages in use, particularly for client-server web applications, with a reported 10 million users.
\n
Java is a general-purpose, object-oriented language that is specifically designed to have as few implementation dependencies as possible. This means that Java programs can run on any device that has a Java Virtual Machine (JVM) installed, regardless of the underlying hardware and software.
\n
Java is a high-level language, meaning that it is easier to read and write compared to low-level languages, which are closer to the machine language that computers understand. Java is also a compiled language, which means that it is transformed into a form that is easier for computers to execute.
\n
Java is known for its simplicity, reliability, and scalability, making it an ideal choice for building large-scale applications. It is also used in a wide range of industries, including financial services, retail, and healthcare.</string>
    <string name="textfp2">\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t<b>  USES OF JAVA </b>
\n
        1) Web and application development: Java is a popular choice for building web and mobile applications, due to its platform-independence, scalability, and security features.
\n
2) Financial services: Java is widely used in the financial industry, particularly for building trading platforms, risk management systems, and other financial applications.
\n
3) Retail: Java is used in retail to build point-of-sale (POS) systems, inventory management systems, and other applications.
\n
4) Healthcare: Java is used to build healthcare information systems, such as electronic health record (EHR) systems, as well as other medical software.
\n
5) Big data: Java is often used in big data environments for tasks such as data processing and analysis.
\n
6) Android development: Java is the primary language used for building Android apps.
\n
7) Scientific applications: Java is used to build a variety of scientific and research applications, including simulations, data analysis tools, and more.
\n
8) Cloud computing: Java is a popular choice for building cloud-based applications due to its scalability and security features.
    </string>

    <string name="navigattion_open">open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigattion_close">close navigation drawer</string>

</resources>